{
    "id": "540bb40f649f4778be7fa166023232ff",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him yesterday.",
            "description": "The present perfect cannot be used with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. to the park last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must ……………………. the instructions.",
            "description": "To listen to is to pay attention to hear.",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "listen to",
                "hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Always …………………. the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "tell",
                "say",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Her dad died two years ……………………",
            "description": "Ago is used to count from a present moment to a past moment. ",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. that movie last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… to the boss about my holiday.",
            "description": "When there is no time reference, the present perfect is more commonly used to talk about finished events. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "have spoken",
                "had spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………… for murder.",
            "description": "The past tense of hang is hanged when we are talking about killing someone by hanging. ",
            "answers": [
                "hanged",
                "hung",
                "hunged"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… the pictures on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hang",
                "hanged"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… under the tree.",
            "description": "When lie means to recline, its past tense is lay. ",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lie",
                "lied",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard them ........................... in the other room.",
            "description": "Hear is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "to talk"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He reached the station after the train ……………………..",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}